AMANDA FOX

Business Professional

SUMMARY

Self-motivated business professional with 5+ years of experience in hyper-competitive market environments. Eager to bring my skills and integrity to an accomplished organization where I can continue to learn and embrace new concepts that better myself, my company and my customer's experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales Representative at Cintas | Houston, TX

October 2018 — Present

- Consistent track record of exceeding goals by 10-20% and receiving quarterly performance bonuses.
- Sales Technology Champion responsible for the training and development of sales team in areas including SAP, Dynamics 365, Sharepoint, Business Process Change Initiatives, etc.
- Focus on driving Process Improvement, Lean, and Six Sigma principles to business operations in order to achieve measurable improvements across sales organization.
- Active mentor to Sales Representatives and Management Trainees.
- Collaborate with champions across organization to define, measure, and improve business processes, while recognizing and documenting tangible results.
- Develop and deliver persuasive presentations to solve business problems, increase sales volume and customer engagement.
- Work closely with service teams to exceed customer expectations, resulting in an annual retention rate of 97%.

Software Engineer at 100Devs | Remote

May 2022 — Present

- Work with languages such as Javascript, SQL, HTML5, and CSS3.
- Collaborate with a team of developers to build modern and responsive web applications using best practices.
- Build semantically structured web applications.

Recent Projects: SpaceCity StarGazers Web App with NASA API integration, Cocktail Recipe Generator with Cocktail DB API integration, Makeup Designs by Lana Web App, and many more.

Management Trainee at Cintas | Houston, TX

January 2017 — October 2018

- Increased sales volume by 102% in assigned territory, ranked in the top 5% of the company.
- Led and managed sales team of 3.
- Managed projects as Product Champion overseeing new product launches, implementation and deadlines.
- Researched and prepared presentations for C-level executives regarding industry trends, competitor analysis, profitability reports, and internal operating inefficiencies.
- Conducted data analysis on product performance, identified areas of improvement, presented incentive programs resulting in 20% product growth...

CONTACT

832.654.5237

amandafox022@gmail.com

amandafox.dev

github.com/amandxfox

linkedin.com/in/amanda-fox-afox

SKILLS

SAP & CRM

SQL

HTML5

CSS3

Javascript

UI/UX

MS Office

Detail-oriented

Project Management

Coaching & Mentoring

AWARDS

8x Summit Club

9x Pinnacle Club

400K Club

Winner's Circle

Rookie of the Year

CERTIFICATION

Six Sigma Green Belt

EDUCATION

SFA State University

2012 - 2016

Degree: BBA General Business

Activities: 4-Year D1 Soccer

Scholarship Recipient